musicnmovies.info 2016-11-06

# » Privacy Policy Bollywood Movies Anytime, Anywhere on Any Device

Effective from Jan/01/2015 

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the bollytalkies.com. On some pages, you can register to view the content. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Email address  
Your IP Address

**The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when registering in the forum ONLY. We do not share this information with outside parties, unless required to present for Legal concerns.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

_We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  
_

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under age of 13, unless provided necessary Guardian Permission in written form. (COPA)

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online(in the forum)and maintain by entering into your forum control panel. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, send us an email at bollytalkies.in@gmail.com
